Aditya Parab

Test Automation Engineer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adiparab14/

Summary

Experienced Automation Test Lead with a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology and Services industry. Skilled in Agile Methodologies, Test Automation and Test Management. Strong quality assurance professional with Masters in Electronics.

Skills

Automation Test and Performance Jenkins

Testing Defect Test

Management

VBScript Java Selenium Postman

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services / Test Automation Lead

May 2016 - Present, Amsterdam

- Test Automation Lead for a Domain within the Bank
- Responsible for Planning and Defining the Strategy for Test Automation for all applications
- Responsible for implementation of Test Automation in the Scrum and Project teams
- Implemented Automation for multiple Applications using HP UFT
- Implemented Automated Execution as part of CICD pipeline involving parallel execution of Test set on Cloud Farm
- Involved with Test Automation COE at organization level in multiple Proof of Concepts to standardize new features for the Automation Framework

Tata Consultancy Services / Test Lead and Team Lead

Jan 2015 - Apr 2016, Amsterdam

- Part of an Important Project within Mortgages Domain of the Bank
- Successfully tested multiple releases as a part of the Project Test Team
- Responsible for planning as well as End to End Test execution
- Involved in Functional as well as Non-Functional Testing
- Also involved in Implementations and solving Post Implementation issues
- Used tools like HP ALM, HP Performance Center and HP UFT

Tata Consultancy Services / Test Engineer

Jul 2011 - Dec 2015, Mumbai

- Involved in Functional and Performance Testing of a Mortgage Advisory and Financial Advisory application
- Analysed Requirements, created Test Plans and executed Test Cases
- Coordinated with onsite Test Lead and Developer Lead
- Involved as a HP LoadRunner Expert at Domain level and provided solutions for multiple Cross Domain applications

Education

M.Tech Electronics / Mumbai University

2009 - 2011, Mumbai, India

B.E. Electronics and Telecommunication / Mumbai University

2005 - 2009, Mumbai, India

Certification

ISTQB Foundation Level

Interests

Running - Training for the past 1 year and participated in various runs including Dam to Dam

Reading - Follow multiple Testing related blogs and like to read about new technologies